<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anthea Li</title>
    <description>Anthea's blog, use Jekyll and github pages.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/liych/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/liych/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 18:39:57 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 18:39:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Augmented Reality 3D Sculpture Retrofitting Stablization Project</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Existing techniques for stability analysis and stabilization solutions for priceless art pieces or historical artifacts require complicated hardware setup and time-consuming support design process. In this paper, we present a novel approach to objects stabilization by integrating Augmented Reality (AR) technology in the traditional stabilization pipeline. Our model solves the 3D model stabilization problem by utilizing AR-enabled real-time photogrammetry to obtain a 3D mesh of the object. Based on the reconstruction, we conduct a stability analysis in real-time to be visualized using AR for users to set their preference on the retrofitting mesh to be designed and generated. Our model constructs a support structure in real-time subjected to user-specified preferences on the minimum tipping angle, maximum amount of support material used and so on. Finally, our model will generate a properly-scaled mesh ready to be 3D printed and attached to the sculpture or model in question for added stability. We demonstrate that the 3D-printed support structure generated by our model provides the same amount of stability as the the existing efforts in sculpture and model stabilization but is a lot faster, less costly, and more convenient than the state-of-the-art system&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/Jalpc/static/assets/img/blog/ARproj/image5.png&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note comment: applied a bug fix similar to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Atlas7/atlas7.github.io/commit/6659f4a47f6ec66987adb0f683a9c6f3842252ae#diff-818954a41dbfb01af70050a459c603b9&quot;&gt;this commit&lt;/a&gt; to ensure code snippet does not collapse unexpectly upon clicking on it. This issue is tracked &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jarrekk/Jalpc/issues/97&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/liych/html/2018/10/31/AR3DRetrofit.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/liych/html/2018/10/31/AR3DRetrofit.html</guid>
        
        <category>Jalpc</category>
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        
        <category>HTML</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Project2&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/liych/html/2017/01/31/3-project2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/liych/html/2017/01/31/3-project2.html</guid>
        
        <category>Jalpc</category>
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        
        <category>HTML</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
